<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Connor Selna</title>
    <link>http://www.example.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Connor Selna</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language><atom:link href="http://www.example.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>http://www.example.com/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.example.com/about/</guid>
      <description>Hi! I&amp;rsquo;m a PhD student at Northwestern University focused on parallel and heterogeneous architectures. I work with Professor Nikos Hardavellas under the PARAG@N lab&amp;rsquo;s Constellation project. I develop novel architectures which leverage explicit parallelism primitives in high-level languages to facilitate faster and more energy-efficient massively-parallel computation.
I also attended Northwestern for my Bachelor of Science in Computer Engineering, for which I was advised by Russell Joseph and in which I focused on computer architecture and microcontroller systems.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>http://www.example.com/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.example.com/contact/</guid>
      <description>Email: connorselna2021 at u.northwestern.edu</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Projects</title>
      <link>http://www.example.com/projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.example.com/projects/</guid>
      <description>VELMA: Vector Element Load Melding Accelerator
When vectorized loads are performed via indirect addressing, particularly as scatter/gather operations, significant spatial locality is overlooked. Consider the case in which two elements in a vector many, many indices apart, are each within the same cache line in memory. Why perform a load on that cache line twice while satisfying one vectorized load? VELMA aims to accelerate vectorized scatter/gathers by melding&amp;ndash;or packing&amp;ndash;the vectorized loads, while preserving program semantics and ordering.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
